Would you go back to Gaza? In a heartbeat. In an absolute heartbeat. My heart is in
Gaza. It will stay in Gaza. The Palestinian people that I worked with, both our national
staff in the office as well as my staff at Indonesia Hospital, were some of the most
incredible people I've ever met in my life. When everything went off and we got the notice
to move south of Wadi, Gaza, I was texting my nurses at Indonesia Hospital and I said,
we lost a nurse weekend one. He was killed when the ambulance outside the hospital was
blown up. And I was texting them when we got the evacuation orders and I said, did any of
you move south? Did any of you get out? Like, are any of you coming down this way? And the
only answer I got was, this is our community. This is our family. These are our friends.
If they're going to kill us, we're going to die saving as many people as we can. And I
said, if I can ever have an ounce of the heart that you have, I will die a happy person.
They were incredible. My doctors and nurses didn't leave out of loyalty to their community.
And I know that there is an idea being pushed right now that anyone that stayed behind is
going to be considered some kind of a threat. And I want to remind people that the people
that stayed behind are heroes. The people that stayed behind are, they know they're going
to die and they're choosing to stay behind anyway.
You're talking about doctors, nurses in the hospital?
I wake up every morning and I send out a text message and I ask, are you alive? And every
night before I go to sleep, I send another message and says, are you alive?
Well, Kelly, thank you so much for your time.
Thank you.